I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
（ラジオＤＪ）
お送りしたのは ラジオネーム—
スイカマンのリクエスト
into the world of perfect free
ニューロティカで
「ア・イ・キ・タ」でした
(You ain't no lonely!)
ホント寒い日 続いてますよね
You're gonna say I'm lying
受験生のあなた 風邪
ひかないように 気をつけてね
I'm gonna get the chance
次のリクエストは東京都の
高校受験生 田中幸雄(たなかゆきお)君から
I thought a chance is far from me
イッツ フォー ユー ユキオ
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
ダイイング・ブリード
「マイ ワールド ダウン」
(I was made to hit in America)
I was made to hit in America
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
（田辺(たなべ)）ムフッ
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
ウハッ ぐっ！
（コユキ）おっ！
（女子生徒）ドスケベ！
（田辺）ブフッ！ ぐっ…
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
大丈夫か？ あっ
I was made to hit in America
（女子生徒）ふっ 変態！
"Knowing someone is reading this."
"Taitou Senior High School."
"Absolute Success!!"
That cool song was requested
by radio listener, Suikaman,
Neurofika's "Aikita."
It's been awfully chilly lately, huh?
To students studying for entrance exams,
please don't catch a cold.
Our next request comes
from Yukio Tanaka in Tokyo.
It's for you, Yukio.
"My World Down" by Dying Breed.
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
Creep!
Are you all right?
-Pervert!
-I'm okay, but my camera's dead.
（田辺）大丈夫 カメラは死守した
甘酸っぱい青春の思い出を
ゲットするために—
I wanted some bittersweet memories
of the days of my youth,
多少のリスク…
so I had to take a bit of a risk...
（兵藤(ひょうどう)の取り巻き１）お～い 田辺
（田辺・コユキ）ん？
-Hey Tanabe!
-Huh?
（取り巻き１）桃(もも)ちゃんが
女子大生のとき—
That rumor about Momo-chan...
ランパブで バイトしてたって
ウワサさ～
that she used to work part-time
in a cabaret club in college...
（コユキ）え…！
（取り巻き２）マジネタなのか？
Is it for real?!
もう気になっちゃって
受験勉強どころじゃねえぜ～
It bothers me so much
I can't study at all!
まあまあ 落ち着けってえ
Calm down guys.
その件に関しては
もう少し時間をくれ
Give me a little more time to check it out.
卒業までには 必ず
証拠をつかんでみせる
I'll find proof before graduation.
じっちゃんの名に懸けて
I swear it on my grandpa's good name.
お前のじっちゃんって… 誰？
Who's your grandpa?
鉄道の職員
He's a railway employee.
（取り巻きたち）ふ～ん
（田辺）ん？
-Hmm...
（取り巻き２）じゃあ行くか
Let's go.
（取り巻きたち）お～う
-Yeah.
（コユキ）ランパブかあ…
A cabaret club, huh?
（桃子(ももこ)）で この
12音技法を考案したのが—
And the one who got the idea for this
オーストリアの作曲家
シェーンベルクよ
was Franz Schubert of Austria.
え～ それで…
-And so...
-Huh?
Tanaka-kun!
（桃子）田中君！
（コユキ）あ…
（桃子）ちゃんと聞いてるの？
Are you paying attention?
Umm...
勉強のしすぎじゃない？
たまには 息抜きしなきゃダメよ
Maybe you've been studying too hard.
You have to relax sometimes.
（田辺）よお
（コユキ）はい
Yes.
（田辺）おい おい… グフフ…
お前 志望校どこだ？
-Which school do you wanna go to?
-Huh? Oh...
一応… 大刀(たち)高
I'm trying for Tachi High.
（兵藤）んっ… ふ～ん
俺は徳武(とくたけ)高だ
I'm trying for Tokutake High.
（兵藤）おい 田中 俺を殴れ
（コユキ）えっ？
Hey Tanaka...
-Hit me.
-Huh?
Haven't you wanted to hit me?
お前 俺のこと
殴りたいと思ったろ
Err...Not anymore.
いや 今は別に
（兵藤）前は？
And before?
（兵藤）殴れねえのか 臆病もんが
You can't hit me?
Coward!
何だ それ
What was that?
Your punch is like a girl's.
女みてえだな お前のパンチ
ハァ… フゥ…
ものを創造する人間は
自分の感情を—
People who create things
must express their feelings clearly
or it's not good...
ちゃんと表現しないと
ダメだって—
うちのオヤジが言ってたぜ
My old man used to say that.
あばよ
So long.
（コユキ）兵藤君！
Hyodo-kun!
See you around.
それじゃあ
（兵藤）おう！
Yeah.
As expected, Momoko-sensei broke
into tears during graduation ceremonies.
（コユキ）予想通り 卒業式で
桃子先生は泣き崩れた
And high school entrance exams
ended without much fanfare.
（コユキ）そして 意外に
あっさりと高校受験は終わった
Yukio!
（コユキの母）幸雄！
Hurry or you'll be late
for the entrance ceremony!
急がないと 始業式から遅刻よ～
I know!
（コユキ）分かってるよ
"Private Ichieda Academy
Senior High School"
From today, you are students
of Ichieda Academy
（校長）きょうから皆さんは
一枝(いちえだ)学園の生徒として—
here to study,
participate in sports and clubs.
勉学に スポーツに
精進していくわけですが—
Osamu Kido, whose mentor,
Karl Goch, treated like a son...
木戸(きど) 修(おさむ)が カール・ゴッチから—
息子と呼ばれるように
なった理由を…
"Anime Research Society"
Hey, you seem like one of our kind.
（部員）どう 君？
われわれと同じニオイを
感じるのだが
"Anime Research Society"
No thanks. I don't intend to join a club.
（コユキ）いや 部活
やるつもりないんで
No thanks. I don't intend to join a club.
（サク）おーい コユキ
Hey Koyuki!
Hey Saku!
ああ！ サク！
あ… その髪形って
Look at your hair!
へへっ まあ
高校生ってことで ちょっとね
Well, I'm in high school now,
so I changed it.
Don't go trying to look sexy.
（千葉(ちば)）
勝手に色気づいてんじゃねえよ
Huh?
Lemme at you!
（千葉）こうしてやる
オラ オラァ！ へへっ
-Hah!
-Hey!
（コユキ）うわ！
ちょ… ちょっと！
Shaddup! Trying to act grown-up!
（千葉）うるせえ 何いっちょ前に
カッコつけてやがんだ
100年 早いんだ コンニャロ～
It's 100 years too early, kid!
Hey, that's mean, Chiba-kun! Stop it!
（コユキ）ひどいよ
千葉君！ やめっててば～
ンヘヘヘ ほら こうしてやる
あ～あ せっかく 朝
１時間もかかったのに
Geez! It took me an hour this morning.
Huh? One hour?
（サク）えっ？ １時間…
（鬼形(きがた)）ギャ～！
（コユキ・サク）ん？
（鬼形）先輩～
Senpai! I'm just not good
at signing up members!
クラブの客集めなんて
僕には向いてないです～
Shut up! If our activities end up
in the red, it'll be your fault!
（先輩１）うるせえ
イベントが赤字になったら
てめえのせいだからな！
Moreover...the sign-up fee is too high.
（鬼形）しかも あの
値段の設定には無理が…
-Umm...
-Huh?
（コユキ）あの～！
あ… あの 鬼形君 その…
もうギブアップっていうか
Umm...Kikata-kun...
You should give up already.
（先輩１）んんっ！
（鬼形）う…
Yusuke, he's the one...
祐介(ゆうすけ) こいつだぜ 例の
Yeah, I know.
（椎木(しいき)）ああ 分かってる
（鬼形）ハァ ハァ… ひぃー！
あ 行っちゃったね…
He just up and left...
-I guess we'll be going, too...
-Hey!
じゃあ僕たちも
（椎木）おい
（サク・コユキ）ああっ！
You're Yukio Tanaka,
the sophomore in Group 4?
（椎木）１年４組の田中幸雄だろ
You'll pass out tickets in his place.
お前があいつの代わりに
チケット さばくんだよ
Why me?
（コユキ）何で… 俺が？
（BECK(ベック)の演奏）
Uh! Yeah!
（千葉）アー！ イェー！
You open up the door with negative aura
-Saku and I finished our entrance exams
-You open up the door with negative aura
（コユキ）俺とサクの受験が終わり
今 俺たちは100パーセント—
-and we'll be concentrating
100% on the band.
-You say future is murky indeed...
-and we'll be concentrating
100% on the band.
-I'm sick of hearing gripe.
バンドに集中している
Open up the door with negative aura
-I can't keep practicing
on Saito-san's guitar forever...
-Open up the door with negative aura
（コユキ）いつまでも斎藤(さいとう)さんの
ギターで練習してるのも悪いし—
-I can't keep practicing
on Saito-san's guitar forever...
-If you never change
-I can't keep practicing
on Saito-san's guitar forever...
-I think there is no way my life fizzle out...
-And I've been wanting my own guitar.
そろそろ自分のギターが
欲しいかなって思うんだ
Oh yeah? Then I'll go
with you to shop around.
（竜介(りゅうすけ)）そっか じゃあ
楽器屋 付き合ってやるよ
There's one I wanna see, too.
俺も見たいのがあるんだ
Really?
ホント？
I'll catch up with you later.
（平(たいら)）
俺もあとから行くよ お前らは？
What about you guys?
This is all I need.
俺 これだけ
You being sarcastic?
嫌みか？
Say, don't you get nervous
going into a music store?
（コユキ）ねえ 楽器屋に
入るのって 緊張しない？
You'll get used to it.
（竜介）そのうち慣れるよ
So, what are you after?
（竜介）お前 何 狙ってんだ？
A Stratocaster...Jaguar...
ストラト ジャガー
Jazz Master...
ジャズマスター
Explorer...SG...
エクスプローラー ＳＧ…
ああ 見てると
みんな欲しくなっちゃって
Makes me want all of them!
-This one...a Kayama Yuzo
by Mosrite is good.
-Oh?
（店員）これ モズライトの
加山(かやま)雄三(ゆうぞう)モデルなんて—
いいと思うよ～
No need to rush into it.
We can check out other places.
まあ 慌てんな
ほかんとこも 見てみようぜ
You're right.
（コユキ）そうだね
（店員）んん…
He dissed me!
（店員）冷やかしかよ
Umm...
（少年）あの～ 今度 友達と
バンドを始めるんですけど—
My friends and I are gonna start a band...
We need something called an effector.
エフェクターっていうのが
いるみたいなんで—
買いにきました
あ～ ピンク・フロイドみたいのが
いいかなって 友達が言うんで…
Umm...My friend said something like
what Pink Floyd uses might work for us...
Do you even know what an effector is?
（高野(たかの)）君さあ
エフェクターって
何なのか 分かってんの？
Not only that...get real.
それにさあ 普通に考えてみてよ
You can't produce a sound like
Pink Floyd on a 5000-yen budget.
予算5,000円でピンク・フロイドの音
出せるわけないでしょ
Oh, it doesn't really
have to be Pink Floyd...
うう いや 別に
ピンク・フロイドじゃなくても—
僕的には全然 構わないんですけど
Make up your mind!
（高野）何よ それ
フンッ
（高野）
昨日のタイムマシーン 見た？
Did you see last night's Time Machine?
Van Halen was on.
ヴァン・ヘイレン 出てたよな
Yes.
（コユキ）竜介君
-Ryusuke-kun...That clerk is scary.
-There's no one like them these days...
（コユキ）あの店員さん 何か
怖いくらい 迫力あるよね
（竜介）
よくいるんだよな ああいうの
A lot of 'em are like that.
（竜介）あの～
（高野）ん？
Excuse me...
このきれいな虎の目のレスポール
弾いてみたいんだけど
I want to try out this
pretty Tiger-eye Les Paul.
竜介君 これ“ＡＳＫ(アスク)”って
書いてあるけど—
Ryusuke-kun...this one says 'ask' on
the tag. How much do you think it is?
いくらなのかな
（高野）108万だよ
（コユキ）ええ？
1,080,000 yen.
Huh?
そのレスポールは
59年 ヒストリック
That's vintage 1959 Les Paul
made by the legendary Tom Murphy.
名工 トム・マーフィーの仕事だ
（店員）うむ
Yeah...
（竜介）へえ～
（店員）コラ 勝手に触んな
Hmm...
Hey, keep your hands off!
これをローンの
頭金にするつもりなんだけど
I was going to use this as a down payment.
アハハハ…
（高野）ちょっと
Just a minute...
竜介君 そんな大金 どうしたの？
Ryusuke-kun! How'd you
get so much money?
I was gonna go to the fish farm
after this to buy fish.
このあと 養魚園に
仕入れにいく予定だったんだ
（店員）おおっ 高野さん…
Takano-san...Y-You're amazing.
すっ すごい…！
（高野）おおお…
アアッ ハァ～ アア～
ハァ…
はーい セッティング 終了しました
Okay, this guitar is prepped.
コユキ 弾けよ
Koyuki, play.
（コユキ）
ええっ？ 竜介君 弾いてよ
Huh? Ryusuke-kun, you play.
そっか
Yeah?
こんなに ひずませちゃ
ホントの音が分かんねえぜ
Can't get a true sound
if it's wired like this.
ンハッ… ハァ…
いかが… ですか？
H-How is it?
うん まあまあだな
（高野）あっ…
Yeah...so-so.
（平）お～い 竜介
おっ 高野さん？
Hey, Ryusuke.
Huh? Takano-san.
（高野）お～
平じゃねえか 久しぶりだな
Oh, Taira! It's been awhile.
しっかし 髪 伸びましたねえ
Damn, your hair has grown.
（高野）ああ これな
ホント 前は 丸坊主だったのに
Ah, this? I know. I used to be bald.
ってことは
ファイヤー・ジョーカーは…
-How's Fire Joker?
-We disbanded last year.
（高野）去年 解散したよ
（竜介）解散？
Disbanded?
Yeah...
いやあ バンド結成した
27んときに—
I was 27 when we formed the band
メジャーデビューするまで 髪
切らないって 決心したんだけどな
and I swore I wouldn't cut my
hair until we had a major debut.
アッハハハ… ハァ～…
（平）はあ…
（竜介）へえ～
-Ah...
-Hmm...
アッハハハ… ハァ～…
（平）そうだ コユキは？
Where's Koyuki?
あれ？ あいつどこだ？
Huh? Where'd he go?
一緒じゃなかったのか？
Weren't you together?
いや ちょっと…
Yeah...for a bit.
（平）拳児さんのことは
あんま悪く言うなよ
Don't badmouth Kenji-san.
Huh?
（平）ああ見えても
メンテナンスにかけちゃ—
He may not look it,
but he's tops in maintenance.
超一流なんだからよっ
（竜介）ハハハ 分かったよ
'Kay.
（竜介）おい どうした？
Hey, what's up?
Like it?
（平）気に入ったのか？
（竜介）弾いてみな
Try it out.
（コユキ）何か…
I feel...
何か ギターが
呼んでる気がするんだ
I feel as though the guitar is calling me.
俺のこと
テレキャスかあ でも
このテレキャス 状態が心配だ
A Telecaster?
But you've got to wonder
what kind of condition it's in.
You're right.
そうだなあ
拳児さん
Kenji-san...
（高野）まあな—
Well, if you buy it,
I'll replace the bridge and peg.
買うっていうなら ブリッジも
ペグも 交換するけどな
うーん 何なら
ピックアップも換えてやる
Hmm...I'll even replace the pick-up.
（コユキ）
ホントに!? あ でも俺…
Really?
But I...
お金が…
...don't have the cash.
In the past, Taira came out to help
and really saved me a number of times.
平には昔—
何度もヘルプで 出てもらって
ホントに助かったんだ
だからってわけでもないが—
That's not the reason, but I'm
willing to make you a special loan.
特別なローンを
組んでやってもいいぞ
ありがとう 考えてみます
Thank you! I'll think about it.
（竜介）
おい コユキ 弾いてみろよ
Hey Koyuki...Play it.
（コユキ）あっ や… やっぱ
お三方の前じゃ ちょっと…
G-Geez...I'm embarrassed
to play in front of you three.
（平）何だよ
もったいぶらせやがって
Why'd you act so shy?
Well...
（コユキ）だってさ
"Chinese Restaurant Sing Lung"
（男性客）早くしてくれよ
（女性店員）すみません
-Hurry it up.
-I'm sorry.
（男性客）
ったく いつまで待たせんだよ
（女性店員）
田中君 天心 まだかな
Tanaka-kun...The dumplings?
The customer is waiting.
お客さんが催促してんのよ
（料理人）
おい 田中 丁寧にやれぃ タコ
Hey, Tanaka, put your back into it.
-Right!
-Hurry with the spring rolls!
はい！
（女性店員）春巻き 早く～
（コユキ）ハァ…
あと２時間か
Two more hours.
（コユキ）ん？
（益岡(ますおか)）いった～い
Ouchie!
お～い バイト
スープ作るから 卵 割っとけ
Hey part-timer! I'm making
the soup, so crack the eggs.
Oh, right!
（コユキ）あっ はい！
（コユキ）あんな すごい人だって
プロになれない世界なんだ
In this world, even someone
so amazing couldn't turn pro...
His hair was so long.
あんなに 髪 伸びちゃってるし
"Sant 'Himizu"
いって～っ
Ow...
Huh? If it isn't Tanaka-kun!
（鬼形）あれ～ 田中君じゃ～ん
（コユキ）あ 何してんの？
What're you doing?
I deliver papers.
（鬼形）ん 新聞配達
By the way, are the tickets selling?
そんなことより
チケット 売れてる？
No...I've been busy
with band rehearsals
いや バンドの練習とか忙しくて
何もしてないけど
and haven't done a thing.
Hey, that's bad!
えっ
そ… それはマズいんじゃ…
You have to help, too, Kikata-kun!
鬼形君も手伝ってよ
Oh, I have to deliver
my newspapers. See you!
あ… ああ 俺 新聞
配らないと じゃっ
Huh?
Hey! What's going on?
（椎木）おい どういうこと？
（コユキ）え だから 忙しくって
チケット売る時間がなくて…
I told you, I was so busy,
I couldn't sell tickets.
Oh...
（椎木）ふ～ん
お前 ちょっと 部室に来い
Come to the club office.
I warned him! This is bad! This is bad!
（鬼形）だから忠告したのに
マズい マズいよぉ
（コユキ）先輩たち
もしかして 軽音楽部なんですか？
Is this club for light music?
（先輩１）当たりめえだろ
-Of course!
-We all have perfect music sense.
（先輩２）
俺たち全員 絶対音感だぜ
Oh...
No, these guys aren't like Hyodo.
（コユキ）ウソだ
こいつらは 兵藤たちと違う
It's cool, huh? The Martin D45.
やっぱ いいですよね～
マーチンＤ-45って
-Huh?
Yeah...it's great. That Marching.
まあな やっぱいいな
マーチャンってやつはな
Damn it!
（椎木）まったく
（コユキ）あっ
You make me sick, just like Chiba!
千葉 同様 ムカつく野郎だぜ
（コユキ）ええっ
-Do you know the Death Valley Bomb?
-No...
お前 デスバレーボム 知ってるか？
あ いや…
-What about Michinoku Driver?
-A little...
みちのくドライバーは？
少しなら
-Awright!
-Shiiki!
（椎木）よおし
（コユキ）うっ！
（千葉）椎木!!
（椎木・コユキ）え？
Chiba-kun!
（コユキ）千葉君！
（千葉）でいっ！
（椎木）どわあっ！
Saku!
（コユキ）サク！
オラァ でいっ！ んっ！
You're pitiful, Shiiki!
みっともねえぞ 椎木！
（椎木）チッ 俺の３年連続級長の
野望を阻止したんだ お前が！
You shattered my dream of being
homeroom president three years in a row!
Hey, you've got it wrong!
（千葉）おい おい！
とんだ 逆恨みだぜ
It's not something I was hoping for...
別に俺が 望んだわけじゃねえ
Our teacher chose based on our grades.
成績優秀による 担任の推薦なんだ
You're the homeroom president?
（サク）えっ！
（コユキ）ええ！ 千葉君が級長？
Listen up, Shiiki...
いいか椎木 今度 コユキとサクに
手ぇ出したら 倍返しだぜ
If you ever lay your hands on Koyuki
or Saku you'll regret it big time.
Sorry...You took some knocks there.
ワリィな とばっちり
くわしちまって
-Nah...
-Umm...
（鬼形）あの～
-Huh?
Could you put me on your
list of persons to protect?
僕もぜひ～ 保護者リストに
加えていただけないでしょうか？
Who are you?
（千葉）誰？ チミ
ああ 腹減ったな！
ラーメンでも 食い行くか
I'm hungry! Let's go eat ramen!
-Uh-huh...
Me too.
僕も…
（エディ：英語）〈この前—〉
The other day, some cases of bullets
were sent to me with a letter.
〈手紙に同封されて
薬莢(やっきょう)が送られて来たんだ〉
"Fishing Hole"
Eddy, that sounds so crazy.
You got some manic groupie or somethin'?
（竜介：英語）〈エディ
そいつはクレイジーだな〉
〈ヤバいグルーピーでも
いるのかい？〉
No, no...no. I have a bad hunch.
（エディ）〈いや
何か悪い予感がするんだ〉
The number of cases
were the same number
〈送られてきた薬莢の数が—〉
as bullet marks on Lucille's body.
〈ルシールのボディの
弾痕と同じなんだ〉
Hey that means...
（竜介）〈それって〉
Yeah...
（エディ）イェー…
I think...he found out about that.
〈そうなんだ〉
〈たぶん ヤツにバレた〉
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Wash your face and take the challenge!
（千葉）あそこでさあ—
顔洗うのが 勝負を
分けるんだよね～
"Live 16 'Indies'"
Wash your face and take the challenge!
Paul Newman is so cool!
I wanna be a hustler, too!
いいよな～
ポール・ニューマン
俺もハスラーに
なりたい！